[
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of France?",
    "answers": ["Paris", "London", "Berlin", "Madrid"],
    "correctAnswer": "Paris"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 + 2?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4 + 2?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1 + 2?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 3 + 2?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 3 + 3?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4 + 1?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 + 0?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4 - 1?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4 + 0?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 + 2 + 2?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 + 2 + 1?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1 + 1 + 1?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1 + 1 + 2?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1 + 2 + 1?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 - 2?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is (2 - 6) - 1?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 + 0 + 1?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 + 0 + 4?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 6 + 0?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 + 2 + 0?",
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  }
]
